{
    "subject": "resource/Balwant_Singh_(footballer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Hoshiarpur",
    "human_readable": "Balwant Singh was born in Hoshiarpur.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8781191110610962,
            "question": "Where was Balwant Singh born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5413464307785034,
            "question": "What is Balwant Singh known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5298872590065002,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Balwant Singh's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3778187036514282,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Balwant Singh's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35984525084495544,
            "question": "How did Balwant Singh contribute to his community?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3554375171661377,
            "question": "What is Hoshiarpur known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35173729062080383,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Balwant Singh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3417588174343109,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Hoshiarpur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3338973820209503,
            "question": "Are there any notable events associated with Balwant Singh's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2657968997955322,
            "question": "What is the history of Hoshiarpur?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Balwant Singh was born in Hoshiarpur.",
            "html": "dbpedia_450_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable events associated with Balwant Singh's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_450_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous people from Hoshiarpur?",
            "html": "dbpedia_450_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Balwant Singh?",
            "html": "dbpedia_450_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_450_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_450_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_450_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_450_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_450_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_450_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_450_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_450_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_450_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_450_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found the following documents related to Balwant Singh:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_450/re-ranker-msmarco/46.txt, it is mentioned that \"Balwant Singh was born on 15th December in the year 1986.  He was born in Hoshiarpur, Punjab.\"\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_450/re-ranker-msmarco/89.txt, it is mentioned that \"Balwant started his footballing journey with Mahilpur Football Club before joining the academy of JCT before being promoted to their senior team in 2008. He was born in Hoshiarpur, Punjab.\"\n\nThe information in these documents supports the triple:\n\n\"Balwant Singh was born in Hoshiarpur.\"\n\nSo, my response is:\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Balwant Singh was born in Hoshiarpur, Punjab. Both the document with path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_450/re-ranker-msmarco/65.txt` and the document with path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_450/re-ranker-msmarco/89.txt` provide information supporting this fact."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}